I want to be a billionaire so fucking bad by all of the things I never had.
I want to be on the cover of Forbes magazine, smiling next to Oprah and the Queen.
Oh, every time I close my eyes, I see my name in shining lights.
Yeah, a different city every night.
Oh, I swear the world better prepare for when I'm a billionaire.
Yeah, I would have a show like Oprah.
I would be the host of Everyday Christmas.
Give me a wish list.
I probably pull a Angelina and Brad Pitt and adopt a bunch of babies that ain't never had shit.
Give away a few Mercedes like, here, let me have this.
And last but not least, grant somebody's last wish.
It's been a couple months that I've been single.
So you can call me Travie Claus.
Midas the ho ho.
Get it?
I'll probably visit with Katrina hit and damn sure do a lot more than FEMA did.
Yeah, can't forget about me, stupid.
Everywhere I go, I might have my own theme music.
Every time I close my.
Eyes.
What you see, what you see I see my name in shining lights.
I guess.
Yeah.
What else?
A different city every night.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Swear the world better prepared for when I'm a billionaire.
Oh oh, when I'm a billionaire.
Oh.
Oh, God.
I'll be playing basketball with the president.
Dunking on his delegates.
And I compliment him on his political etiquette.
Toss a couple million in the air just for the heck of it.
But keep the 520 tens and bins completely separate.
Yeah, I'll be in the whole new tax bracket.
We in recession.
But let me take a crack at it.
I probably take whatever's left and just split it up.
So everybody that I love can have a couple bucks and not a single tummy around me would know what hungry was.
Eatin good, sleeping soundly.
I know we all have a similar dream.
Go in your pocket, pull out your wallet, put it in the air and sing.
I wanna be a billionaire.
So fucking bad, so bad.
By all of the things I never had.
Everything I wanna be on the cover of Forbes magazine.
Smiling next to Oprah and the Queen.
What up Oprah?
Oh, every time I close my eyes.
What you see, what you see, bruh I see my name.
In shiny lights.
And what else?
A different city every night.
Yeah, yeah, yeah I swear the world better prepare.
For when I'm a billionaire.
Yeah.
Oh oh.
Singing when I'm a billionaire.
I want to be a billionaire.
So fucking bad.