We were good.
We were cold.
Kind of dream that can't be sold.
We were right till we weren't.
Built a home and watched it burn.
I didn't wanna leave you I didn't wanna lie.
Started to cry but then remembered I.
I can buy myself flowers.
Write my name in sand.
Talk to myself for hours.
See things you don't understand.
I can take myself dancing and I can hold my own.
Yeah I can love me better than you can love me.
I can love you better, baby.
Love me better.
I can love me, baby.
Hey.
My nails.
Cherry red.
Match the roses that you left.
No remorse, no regret I forgive every word you say.
Ooh, I didn't wanna leave you baby I didn't wanna fight.
Started to cry but then remembered I.
I can buy myself flowers.
Write my name in sand.
Talk to myself for hours.
He'll see things you don't understand.
I can take myself, daddy.
There.
I can hold my own here.
Yeah, I can love me better than you can love me.
I love you better, baby.
You love me better.
I can love you better, baby.
I can love me better, baby.
You love me better.
I didn't want to leave you.
I didn't want to fight.
Started to cry, but then remembered I.
I can buy myself flowers, write my name in the sand, talk to myself for hours.
Say things you don't understand.
Well, I can take myself dancing.
Yeah, I can hold my own in there.
I can love me better than.
Yeah, I can love me better.
You can't.
Can love me better.
I can love me better baby than you can, uh I Can Love, baby?
Can Love me better.
I.