(Transcribed by Sonix.ai - Remove this message by upgrading your Sonix account) For what that is worth.
But lately I've been doing better then the
last four cold Decembers I recall.
And I see my family every month.
I found a girl my parents love.
She'll come and stay the night.
And I think I might have it all.
And I thank God every day for the girl he
sent my way.
But I know the things he gives me, he can
take away.
In I hold you every night, and that's a
feeling I won't get used to.
But there's no man as terrified as the man
who stands to lose you.
Oh, hope I don't lose you.
Please stay.
I want you, I need you.
Oh, God.
Don't take.
It is beautiful.
Things that I've got.
Please stay.
I want you, I need you.
And you'd take these beautiful things that
I've gone.
Please don't take.
I found my mind.
I'm feeling sane.
It's been a while, but I'm finding my face.
If everything's good and it's great.
Why do I sit and wait till it's gone?
Oh, I tell you I know I've got enough.
I've got peace and I've got love.
But I'm up at night thinking I just might
lose it all.
Oh. Please stay.
I want you, I need you.
Oh, God. Don't take these beautiful things
of God.
Stay.
Please stay.
I want you, I need you.
Oh, God, I need.
These beautiful things that I've got. (Transcribed by Sonix.ai - Remove this message by upgrading your Sonix account)