I've been known to miss a red flag.
I've been known to put my love on a pedestal.
In the end, those things just don't last.
And it's time I take my rose colored glasses off.
I already know you take to me the things I'd like to see.
Maybe you feel like taking me for a ride.
Know your time.
Think about your kids, right?
Don't you know I could do this dance all night?
Ooh.
What you doing?
Don't know who you think that you're confusing.
I'd be like, ooh.
It's amusing.
You think I'm gonna fall for an illusion?
Hey.
No, no.
No.
Dance.
No!
I'd be lying.
Dance all night.
Dance.
This was the time when that she might have worked.
Was the time when I just threw a match and let it burn.
Now I'm grown I know what I deserve I still like dancing with the lessons I already learned I know your type.
Two things I like truly make me yours for life.
Take me for a ride.
Enjoy your time.
Think about your country.
Don't you know I could do this dance all night?
Ooh.
What you doing?
Don't know.
Who do you think that you're confusing?
I'd be like, ooh, it's amusing.
You think I'm gonna.
Fall for an aloof.
Oh, what a shame.
Hey, dance all night.
Have you left it so late?
Dance all night.
Is this.
Losing?
I really like the way you're moving.
Yeah.
I just wanna dance with the loser.
Yeah I just wanna dance with.
Yeah, I just wanna dance with I could dance all night.
Hey.
So what you do when you don't know who you think that you're confusing?
I'd be like, ooh, it's amusing.
You think I'm gonna fall for it?
Oh.
What you.
Doing?
Don't know who you think that you're confusing.
I'd be like, ooh, it's amusing.
You think I'm grateful for it?
Or do.
Asian.